http://www.peopletree.co.uk/policies/privacy

End of Season Sale, Now On!
Loading...
BAG
(0)
What You Can Expect From Us
People Tree believes purchasing items online should be as secure as shopping in-store and we strive to achieve this through being compliant with our Privacy Policy. We respect your privacy rights and protect all online visitor personal information.
People Tree is registered under the General Data Protection Regulation and the Data Protection Act 2018 and we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We work hard to ensure that People Tree only use your information in the ways that you have agreed. This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us and is part of our Terms and Conditions. If you are under 18, we require that you inform a guardian or parent regarding People Tree privacy policy before ordering online.
Personal data will be processed:
Lawfully
Fairly
Transparently
How We Use Information
When you place an order with us we require certain information, such as personal details, order, address(es) and payment particulars, so that we can process your transaction and deliver your goods.
In order to give our customers the best possible service, we may at times ask for other details, for example, product size and category preferences, age and any special dates (such as birthday). This is entirely voluntary and we only use this information for profiling and marketing purposes.
You can choose to sign up for our regular email newsletter and to receive other marketing communications from us via post, email, SMS, MMS and telephone. We will only use the contact method to which you have agreed.
We are always interested in improving and developing our website and may contact you requesting feedback regarding your online experience. For quality control and training purposes, we may monitor or record your communications with us. This information will only be kept for as long as is reasonably necessary for these purposes.
We may use information collected about you in the following ways:
In order to process your order and deliver your purchases we may have to pass your information to some of our service providers, such as our order dispatch service and our delivery company. Our courier company will be informed of your telephone number as they may wish to contact you by phone or text message to update you on the delivery date and time of your order. Any details passed on to these third parties will only be used in the prescribed way and cannot be used by these companies in their own right.
To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you.
To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
To inform you of any special offers, competitions and promotions.
To send you catalogues or other marketing material.
In certain circumstances
we may need to use your information in the detection or prevention of fraudulent activity. This may involve disclosing your address and postcode details to check against IMRG Security Alert or any other Fraud Prevention Scheme.
We may ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them. Personal data processed for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.
Use of Cookies
From time to time, we may collect anonymous information about your browsing behavior on our site in order to improve our service to you. We may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on your browser or the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. If you register with us or if you continue to use our site, you agree to our use of cookies.
You may block cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse all or some cookies. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon you visit our site.
We use cookies to offer you personalized advertising. You can also opt-out of this at any time by clicking the pop up to the right of this screen. If you choose to opt-out, a cookie will be placed on your computer to indicate that no information is to be collected by us about you, although this will not prevent ads or pop-ups on your computer by other companies. Please note that you would need to repeat this process for each browser and computer that you use. If you delete an opt-out cookie, you would need to repeat the process again to express your preference.
This Website Uses Remarketing
This website uses various remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to previous visitors to our site. This could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site for marketing purposes.
This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page,or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the peopletree.co.uk website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
AdWords Remarketing is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google. It connects the activity of peopletree.co.uk with the Adwords advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie. You can opt out of the cookie tracking here: http://google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en
Personal Information
The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. Access to customer account information is limited to staff who require immediate access to process orders. We use full login and password controls to protect the information held. Our site uses secure server software to protect your information. All information is encrypted and protected in accordance with the law.
The transmission of information via the internet is however not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site. Any transmission is at your own risk.
Disclosure of Your Information
We will not pass your information to any third parties outside of People Tree Ltd, except where required to do so as a part of the sale, disposal or transfer of our business, in whole or in part.
We will not pass your personal details on to a third party brand for marketing purposes unless you choose to opt in for 3rd party marketing. If you do opt in, from time to time and only with your permission, we may disclose your information including name, address and email address available to other companies whose products are similar to ours.
If you do not wish to receive any third party emails, please do not tick the third party marketing preference box when registering online, if you have previously ticked for 3rd party marketing and now have changed your mind please go to your preferences center and untick this box or let us know when ordering over the phone and we will do this for you.
In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of People Tree, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Your Rights
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. You can exercise the right at any time by contacting us or by unsubscribing from our email newsletters and/or catalogue by changing your preferences in your People Tree account. You have the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act.
Contact Us
Should you wish to gain a copy of the personal information we hold on you (for which we may charge a small fee) please contact us on the below channels. We welcome your questions, comments and requests regarding our Privacy Policy. If you need more information about our privacy policy or if you need assistance unsubscribing from our email newsletters and/or catalogues, please send us an email or give us a call.
TELEPHONE
Call: 0845 450 4595 or 020 7042 8900
Office hours are 9:30 am to 5:00 pm Monday to Friday. We are closed on weekends and on bank holidays.
To reach us outside normal business hours, leave a voice message and we will return your call or send us an email.
EMAIL
Send your message to people@peopletree.co.uk
ADDRESS
We are located at People Tree Ltd, 26 Camden High St, Kings Cross, London NW1 0JH
